(Penny:)You're the best dad ever.
(Penny's Dad:)Yeah. Uh, hold that thought.
(Penny's Dad:)I've been sitting
on a little news myself.
(Penny:)Well, what is it?
(Penny's Dad:)You know that rototiller
I got for the tractor?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Penny's Dad:)Oh, you should see it.
(Penny's Dad:)It is a beautiful
piece of machinery.
(Penny's Dad:)Anyway, uh...
(Penny's Dad:)I backed over
your pet pig with it.
(Penny:)Moondance?
(Penny's Dad:)Yeah, he's, uh,
not dancing anymore.
(Penny:)You killed my pig?
(Penny's Dad:)I did not kill him.
(Penny's Dad:)The vet took care of that.
(Penny's Dad:)When?
Oh... ten, 12 months ago.
You didn't tell me for a year?!
(Penny's Dad:)Well, apple doesn't fall far
from the tree, does it?
(Penny's Dad:)Love ya, slugger.
Gotta go!
(Bernadette:)Okay, Amy, your turn.
(grunting)
(breathing rhythmically)